It's a new white-living record!
You're so strong!
I'm not strong!
So strong!
That's so light I could lift it up with my finger!
Oh my! But do you think you could lift up your nightstand?
Don't know. Never tried it.
So then go on!
No way!
And you are so much bigger than that nightstand!
But watch, I can lift this big pencil!
And just look how much smaller I am!
So, who's stronger, you or me?
Well, I guess it's not me.
The Fixies may be very small,
but they are actually much stronger than humans!
Yes, it's true!
What, you don't believe me?
Well, who's stronger, an elephant or an ant?
You think it's the elephant.
Well, of course, it's so much bigger!
But did you know that one ant can lift up 50 ants its own size?
And an elephant? It can't even hold up one!
So it turns out that for its size an ant is much stronger than an elephant.
And the same goes for Fixies.
Fixies are incredibly strong for their size.
They can lift things that are a hundred times heavier than they are.
And Fixies can jump 50 times higher than their own height!
If humans were as strong as Fixies are,
They'd be able to lift an automobile all by themselves!
Yeah, Tom Thomas, it's time you built up your strength!
Well, how?
Start lifting dumbbells!
Or if you want to, you can use my barbell.
No, thanks.
I'll use the dumbbells my dad has.
They're in his office, I think.
Oh, there's one!
And where's the other one?
Aha! There you are! I'll get you out of there!
Come on, come on!
I'm helping you here!
It's stuck!
Alright!
Move aside!
I'll get it right out!
What is this? Glue to the floor or something?
Hey!
What's all the racket?
Hi there, Simka!
We can't get the dumbbell out from under there.
Well, of course you can't. The sofa is pressing down on it.
So that's what it is.
And I was worried that I lost all my strength.
Well, that means we have to lift up this sofa.
We can't do that. It's too heavy for us.
We can do it.
Tom Thomas, get me your hockey stick from your room.
We can't move a sofa with a hockey stick?
Don't worry, you'll see.
Here, I've brought it.
What is it for?
We're going to use it as a lever.
A lever?
Well, yeah!
A lever works the same way that a seesaw does
with a board resting on top of a piece called the fulcrum.
But with a lever one side is longer than the other.
And that's the secret to its power!
With a lever's help it's possible to lift any weight.
All you need to do is get the short arm of the lever under the load
and push down on the long arm.
And the longer the arm, the more weight you can lift.
And that's how a lever makes people stronger!
Well, can we find a fulcrum in here?
Maybe the stumbo. Can that be our fulcrum?
Great idea!
Now you're thinking the right way.
You ready to go?
Let's go!
Lean on it, Tom Thomas!
Yay! It's working!
Tideesh!
I'm so strong! Did you see?
Now watch how I lift Dad's heavy weights for you.
Look! I can do it!
It's just like I told you! You'd be better off training with my weights!
Didn't you just see me lift up the sofa?
You didn't lift the sofa, the lever did!
Did you ever hear the saying,
knowledge is power?
I've heard it.
Although, some physical power won't hurt you either.
So pick up your lever and go out and play some hockey!
You know how built those hockey players are!